哦 好疼!
Ooh,it hurts!
求你了... 幫幫我
Please... Help me.
哦 我的天啊! 不要啊!
Oh,my god! Stop!
帶我去醫院吧
Take me to a hospital.
住手! 哦 我的老天 不要!
Stop! Oh,my god,stop!
一切還好嗎?
Is everything ok?
哦 天哪
Oh,god.
嘿 小寶貝 你好啊
Hey,you. Hoyou doing?
把孩子給我 等等
Give me the baby. Wait.
是個女孩 不要啊! 不要! 就讓我
It's a girl. Don't! No!Let me just
把孩子還給我!
give me back my baby!
下個是什麼?
What's next?
巴吞魯日市自覺出現 白人至上主義的現象
Baton rouge thinks they have a white supremacist problem.
你的想法呢? 我怎麼想的?
What's your take? Really?
是啊 我想聽聽你的意見
Yeah,i'd like to hear it.
我覺得是個人憤恨 不是團體行為 怎麼講?
We're dealing with an individual,not a group. Why?
許多充滿憤怒情緒的信件
The angry letters.
作者的代詞形式從複數變成了單數
The writer switches pronouns from plural to singular.
"我們是全副武裝的自衛隊"  "我會被迫採取武力行動"
"we are a heavily armed militia," llowed by,llect ttan."
很好 附上我們的分析一塊寄回警局 還有嗎?
Good. Send it back to the police with our analysis. What else?
你要出去?
You need to be somewhere?
Henry現在很粘我
Henry's just going through a clingy stage.
早上3點給他換的尿布到現在了
It's one less 3 a.M. Diaper change when i put him down.
那你回家吧?
Why don't you go home?
哦 不用不用 就剩5個案子了 解決掉算了
Oh,no,no,no. We only have 5 more cases. We can crank 'em out.
明天也可以的 回家吧
We can do this tomorrow. Please go home.
好吧 謝謝你了
Ok. Thank you.
我把這些發完了就回去
I just have one last distribution and i'm out of here.
晚安 晚安
Good night. Good night.
Strauss主管 Aaron
我們得談談 關上門
Close the door.
我得和局長商量商量
I need to review this with the director.
Jareau探員
Agent jareau.
長官
Ma'am.
Hotch 怎麼?
Hotch. Yes.
沒事吧?
Is everything ok?
是 沒事 晚安
Yes,everything's fine. Good night.
晚安
Good night.
弗吉尼亞州 匡提科 聯邦調查局 行為分析小組
來自: A. Hotchner 新案探討
來自: A. Hotchner 再看下這個
Reid 我錯過什麼了嗎?
Reid,what did i miss?
老兄 你不會相信的 有個白癡 剛發了一博客 叫"Carl Sagan會怎麼辦"
Oh,man,you're no beeve this.
不 Reid 我是說新案子 是什麼案子?
No,reid,the case. What's the case?
你說什麼呢?
What are you talking about?
我收到Hotch的郵件了 "再看下這個"  "新案探討"
These emails from hotch. "take a look at this," "new case to review."
Hotch的郵件?  我沒收到Hotch的郵件啊?
emails from hotch? I didn't get any emails from hotch,did i?
的確沒有
Nothing.
進來
Come in.
你抽空看材料了嗎?
Did you,uh,get a chance to look at the files?
我剛收到 什麼材料這麼重要其他人沒有?
I just got them. What's so important you couldn't send it to the rest of the team?
我只是想聽聽另一個人的意見
I just needed a second pair of eyes.
那我現在就看 一個小時就好
I'll review it right now. Just give men .
沒那個必要 我們準備好了
That's not necessary. We're ready.
Kristie Taylor 在逃吸毒人員 三年前於新墨西哥的法明頓被報失蹤
Kristie taylor, runaway,drug addict, reported missing from farmington,new mexico years ago.
昨天 她被發現在媊鶿鴘滌玟t公路邊
Yesterday,she turned up off a freeway outside of rio rancho.
有性侵犯跡象 腳踝處有捆綁痕跡  是窒息而死的
Sexual assault combined with ligature s marksd ankles. She was phyxiated.
5年中有3名受害人
3 victims in 5 years.
所有受害人身上都有傷痕 他喜歡捆綁
All the women are connected by marks.
一定是性虐待狂
Definite sexual sadist.
兇手遵循套路 都是16至19歲的金髮女
He sticks to his type. 16to 19yearold girls, all blond.
而且在她們身上花了很長時間 注意
Hangs on to them for a while,too. Look at this.
綁架和殺害她們的時間間隔平均2年
Average of 2 years between abducting them and killing them.
殺害人數少 禁錮時間長  這個兇手很有自制力
Low body count, long time frame. This guy's in control of his urges.
也太自製了 虐待狂期盼新的被虐者 喜歡以新的方式折磨她們
Too controlled. Sadists need new victims, new ways to torture.
很多傢伙都喜歡捆綁
There are a lot of guys out there who like chains.
我們能確定這是同一個不明嫌犯嗎?
Are we sure this is the same unsub?
Kristie Taylor的驗屍報告還顯示 這些受害人之間的另一個相同之處
Kristie taylor's autopsy report also indicates a second connection between these victims.
她懷孕了 還生過孩子
She was pregnant. She'd given birth.
生完沒過多久 不明嫌犯就殺了她
Very soon after, the unsub killed her.
有多久? 幾分鐘後
How soon after? Minutes.
這個不明嫌犯不是典型的性虐待狂
This unsub isn't your typical sexual sadist.
我們見過囚禁侵犯被害者的 卻沒見過這樣的個性簽名
Captivity and assault we've seen before.What we haven't seen is this signature
在殺她們之前 他強迫這些女孩扮演的角色
the role he forces these women to fulfill before he kills them.
母親的角色
Motherhood.
犯罪心理 第五季 第05集 從生到死
Criminal Minds Season05 Episode05 Cradle to Grave
記者William D.Tammeus寫道
Journalist william d.Tammeus wrote,
"你不可能真正瞭解人性
"you don't really understand human nature
"除非能理解為什麼旋轉木馬上的孩子 會在每次轉過父母時和他們招手"
"unless you know why a child on a merrygoround "will wave at his parents every time around
而父母也會每次和他們招手"
and why his parents will always wave back."
為什麼性虐待狂會讓那些女孩 懷上他的孩子呢?
so why would a sexual sadist make womenry hhildren?
Gary Heidnik就在地牢堻]置了行宮 (美國20世紀殺人犯 綁架虐待6名婦女)
Gary heidnik kept a harem in a dungeon.
他的目的就是繁衍個大家庭 以替代自己破碎的家庭
His goal was to create a large family as a replacement for his own broken home.
Josef Fritzl把親生女兒關在家 他們還一起生了好幾個孩子
Josef fritzl kept his daughter in a cell in his own house, and they had several kids together.
糟糕的處境是他們 控制欲幻想的部分原因
Squalid conditions are part of a control fantasy these men had.
如果他把這些女孩安置在同一地點 就需要很多私人空間
If he's keeping these women in a similar location, he'd need a lot of privacy.
也許他自己蓋了個地方 手一定很巧
He probably built it himself. Makes him good with his hands.
為什麼都是金髮 對他有什麼特殊意義?
Why blondes, and what significance do they have to him?
也許是 嗯 拒絕過他的女人 或是不願懷上他孩子的女人?
Maybe,uh,the woman who rejected him or the woman who wouldn't bear his children?
如果是這樣 他就應該 和這些女孩同齡 不過20來歲
If that were true,he'd be the same age as these girlslate teens.
可這個不明嫌犯手法太老道了
This unsub is too skilled for that.
那就是他母親?
His own mother,then?
她可能也是個逃犯 和這些受害人一樣
She could be a runaway, just like these victims.
這就孕育了他的強迫心理
Which makes his compulsion psych 101
一次又一次地殺了她 就因為她生下他
killing his mother over and over again for giving birth to him.
是啊 可為什麼要等到她生完呢?
Yeah,but then why wait until after she gives birth?
這下他就要搞定一個大人一個孩子了
Now he has a body and a baby to get rid of.
我也很疑惑 我們只找到了母親 卻沒發現嬰兒
,toyeah,but then why wait untiwe found the mothersrth? But not the infants.
呃 我實在不想這麼說 可如果這些女孩 只是他達到最終目的的工具呢?
Uh,i hate to say this, but what if the women are just a means to an end?
如果他要的其實是那些孩子呢?
What if the babies are really the ones he's exploiting?
如果Kristie Taylor是才被發現的 也就是說孩子現在還在他手
If kristie taylor just surfaced, it means he has her baby right now.
JJ 和她們的父母聯繫
Jj,check with the parents.
看看她們的在逃之間有沒有相同之處 看看不明嫌犯是在哪綁走她們
See if there are any similarities in the runaways' patterns, where the unsub's finding them.
Reid和Prentiss 去最近發現的棄屍點
Reid and prentiss, go to the latest dump site.
我們要好好研究被害者類型
We need to look at victimology.
查出她們臨死前他是怎麼做的
How he treats these women in the final moments of their lives
或許能知道他對那些孩子有什麼企圖
might tell us what he's doing to the children.
新墨西哥州 阿爾伯克基
大夫 你的報告上說Kristie流產過好幾次
Doctor,you wrote in your report that kristie had had several miscarriages.
這是怎麼發現的?
How was that evident?
她子宮內壁有好幾處磨損
There were a number of abrasions in her uterine lining.
大概6 7個月時 她的羊水就會破了
Around the third trimester, her water would break.
這麼說她都沒能生下來?
So she never carried to term?
不 最後一次她生下來了
No,last time she did.
她血液中催產素的含量非常高
There was a high level of pitocin in her blood.
那是種人工荷爾蒙 能誘發分娩
It's an artificial hormone. You give it to induce labor.
就是說她被催得很緊?
She was on a tight schedule?
如果孩子流掉了 他就立即再讓她懷上
If she lost the baby, he would get her pregnant again immediately.
生孩子已經夠痛苦的了
Childbirth is tough enough.
更別說把自己的命懸在這上面
Imagine if your life depends upon it.
3個母親都有前科  濫用藥物 酗酒 精神紊亂
All 3 moms had records. Drug abuse, drunk and disorderlies.
不過更有意思的 是她們被綁架後的事
But what's more interesting is what he does after he kidnaps them.
這是Kristie Taylor被綁架2周前
This is kristie taylor 2 weeks before she was abducted.
他幫助她恢復了健康  保持營養 戒掉了壞習慣
He got her healthy. Wellfed and off the habit.
沒完全戒掉
Not completely.
Kristie體內的這些藥物是什麼?
These drugs in kristie's systemwhat are they?
它莫西芬 胃復安 多潘立酮 黃體酮
Tamoxifen,metoclopramide, domperidone,progesterone.
黃體酮是產前藥物 是嗎?
Progesterone's a prenatal medication,isn't it?
以上都是 頭兩種幫助保住胎兒
They all are. The first 2 help carry the baby to term.
後兩種幫助分泌乳汁
The last 2 help with lactation.
什麼樣的性虐待狂 會給受害人服用產前藥物?
Exual sadist gives his victims prenatal drugs?
想要照看孩子的性虐待狂
The kind who takes care of the kids he's having.
他殺了母親 卻非常保護孩子
He gets his rocks off killing the moms, but the babies he protects.
你認為他把孩子留在了身邊?
You think he's keeping them?
如果他拋棄母親 也會拋棄孩子
If he despises the moms, he'd despise their children,too.
新墨西哥地處國界
New mexico's right on the border.
活動著許多人口販子
A lot of human trafficking going on.
既然他讓母親的懷孕節奏這麼快 說明他在繁衍自己的後代
This tight schedule he keeps the moms onhe could be breeding.
打電話給兒童保護組織
Call child protection services.
我們要找出現存的嬰兒販賣黑市
We need to find out about existing black markets for infants.
謝謝
Thank you.
這沒有輪胎印
There's no tire tracks.
屍體並沒有丟在離大路很遠的地方
The body wasn't dumped that far from the road.
這傢伙跟本不在乎別人看見  都不花功夫把屍體藏好點
This guy doesn't care about them, not enough to even hide them very well.
所以沒道理啊
That's why this doesn't make any sense.
不明嫌犯的棄屍點 其實很能說明問題的
Dump sites reveal something about the unsub,you know?
至少 從地點熟悉度來看  他知道自己在這個地方不會被抓
At the very least, a geographic familiarity, a place he knows he won't get caught.
好 這麼說他對這條路很熟
Ok,so he knows this road.
對 可他是在法明頓綁架Kristie的 卻把她扔到了媊鶿
Yeah,except he abducted kristie in farmington and then dumps her here in rio rancho.
相距175英里
開車那麼久 就為把她扔路邊?
Why drive that far just to dump a body by the side of the road?
反偵查策略? 用長距離掩蓋輪胎印?
A forensic countermeasure? Covering his tracks by sheer distance?
所以說關於地理位置的側寫 沒多大幫助
So the geographical profile won't do us much good.
不 還是有幫助的 只是和受害人無關
No,it will, wi the victims.
據我們的側寫 他感興趣的是孩子
We profiled that it's the babies that he's interested in.
他會在這點上暴露自己
That's where he'll reveal himself.
通過他販賣孩子的收養機構 和使用的渠道網絡
The adoption company he sells through and whatever network of resources he uses.
他會圖方便走捷徑
He makes shortcuts there for convenience.
沒人會開車到100英里外買尿布 或者填寫一張出生公證
No one's gonna drive 100 miles for diapers or for a public notary for legal paperwork.
如果孩子記錄在案 就能找到他
If the babies are in the system, they'll lead us to him.
販賣兒童在其他國家很猖獗  不過在這兒 倒是不常見
Child trafficking is huge in other countries, but here it's mostly a myth.
新墨西哥州 阿爾伯克基 兒童保護組織
為什麼?
Why is that?
因為有更簡單合法的途徑收養
There's an easier and legal pathadoption.
會有文件記錄的對不對?
There'd be a paper trail, though,wouldn't there?
要匿名也是有辦法的
There are ways to hide your tracks.
一定有辦法能查到所有孩子
There must be a way to identify all these kids.
每宗收養都有法庭記錄
There's a court record for every adoption.
把記錄給我們 我們先按時間篩選
Give us the records. We'll start weeding them out by date.
本州的收養案件都是保密的
The adoptions in this state are closed.
資料都封好了 要花點時間
The files are sealed. So it'll take time.
我們等不起
That's a luxury we don't have.
眼下有個孩子正處於危險之中
There's a child at risk right now.
所有走過收養程序的孩子
All children who go in and out of the adoption system
都作過出生前基因狀況檢查
get basic genetic screenings for preexisting conditions.
我們這有他們的DNA記錄
We have their dna.
這個也行 我們可以把母親的DNA 和他們的作對比
We can use that. We can match the maternal dna with the babies in the system.
即使這樣也還有好幾百個孩子
We're still talking hundreds of kids.
我們把其中一個孩子的DNA給你們呢?
Uofhe b iies' dna?
那樣就快多了
That would make it go faster,yeah.
這些母親生完孩子後馬上就被他殺了
He kills these moms so soon after they give birth,
屍體上很可能還殘留孩子的DNA
secondary dna could still be on their bodies.
我聯繫法醫
I'll call the m.E.
我理解 謝謝您 大夫
I understand. Thank you,doctor.
Jareau探員?
Agent jareau?
我是Conrad Winmar 這是我太太Jane
I'm conrad winmar. This is my wife jane.
謝謝你們過來
Thank you for coming in.
我們進房間談好嗎?
Why don't we talk privately?
你你想瞭解我們的女兒?
Youyou want to dig up our daughter?
我們認為不明嫌犯也許 在她體內留下了DNA
We think the unsub might have left dna on her.
雖然上兩個受害者沒有
The last 2 victims didn't have any,
但考慮到Monica是第一個 他也許會犯錯
but because monica was the first, he might have made a mistake.
警方發現她的時候 說沒發現兇手的DNA
Back when they found her, the detectives said that they did not find his dna.
我們找的不是他的DNA
It's not his dna we're looking for.
我們懷疑你們的女兒 在被綁架期間生過孩子
We suspect your daughter gave birth while she was captive.
什麼?
What?
不明嫌犯讓所有的受害人都懷孕了
The unsub has gotten all of his victims pregnant.
他也許把孩子送去了收養機構
He might be putting the babies in the adoption system.
孩子還活著? 有可能
The baby's alive? Possibly.
如果我們能找到Monica的胎盤組織
If we could find placental tissue on monica,
我們就可以對其進行DNA檢測並與 州記錄比對
we can test the dna against the state's records.
請授權給我們
Give us the release.
我第一次看見她的同時 也看了她的檔案
The first time i saw her, saw her record,too.
以為她就是那些街頭遊蕩的女孩之一 根本不在乎如何對待自己(的生命)
Thought she was just another girl on the street, t t she did to herself.
我甚至根本沒有想過要查這個
I never even thought to look for this.
這是什麼? 這是嬰兒的臍帶
What is it? It's a baby's umbilical cord.
那孩子現在該四歲左右了
The child should be about 4 now.
我希望你能找到"他"或"她" 真的
I hope you find him or her. I really do.
謝謝你
Thank you.
好 大家都知道 大多數收養孩子的人 幾乎都是世界上最善良和無私的
Ok,know thismost adoption folk are like the nicest, most dedicated people in the world.
但是也會有極個別 齷齪下流低級那種人
There are,however, one or two skeezy ones.
有多齷齪下流低級? 超級齷齪下流低級
How skeezy? Super skeezy.
我這有其中一人發的傳單 要求因為收養的孩子得到報酬
I've got a spread sheet from one of them expecting compensation for the baby i'm having.
你還有什麼要告訴我的嗎 Garcia?
Something you want to tell me,garcia?
哦 說來傷感 我的王子
Oh,that's the sad part, my prince.
有你我完美遺傳基因的寶寶 可賣不上個好價錢
The genetically perfect offspring of penelope garcia and derek morgan wouldn't fetch top dollar.
什麼樣的賣得上? 與有色人種相比 白人嬰兒供不應求
Who does? White babies are in higher demand than minorities.
男孩比女孩更受歡迎  反正至少今年是
Boys are more popular than girls, at least this year,anyway.
然後還有和瑞典選超模一樣的標準
And then there's the swedish supermodel rule.
什麼?
The what?
如果我成功生下金髮藍眼的娃兒 我人生就別無所求了 真的
If i were to deliver a blondhaired,blueeyed bundle of joy, i'd be set for life. I would.
Garcia 新墨西哥州領養記錄媯o現 和嬰兒的DNA匹配的了嗎?
Garcia, did the baby's dna turn up in new mexico's adoption records?
沒 沒有和她的資料匹配的 順便說一下 那是個女孩
No. There's no hits on her profile. And it is a her, by the way.
不明疑犯很可能還在出售嬰兒 只是沒有通過官方渠道
This unsub could still be selling babies, just not through the system.
這也讓抓他的難度更大了
That's gonna make him a lot harder to catch.
好了 不早了 大家都去休息吧 明兒一大早我們再議
All right. It's late. Let's get some rest. We'll hit this fresh in the morning.
Garcia撤了
Garcia out.
Morgan 我希望你提出 一份書面的初步側寫
Morgan. I'd like for you to write up a preliminary profile.
我們掌握的還不夠
We don't have enough for that.
對 所以才是初步側寫
Well,that's why it's preliminary.
進一步側寫過程中 我們能知道漏掉了什麼
A work in progress profile helps show us what we're missing.
好的 沒問題
Ok. Sure.
你現在感覺怎樣?
How you holding up?
我們剛浪費了一整天去查 一個可能不存在的黑市
We just wasted a day looking into a black market that probably doesn't exist.
我不是問這個 我聽說 你受到不少壓力
At's nothat i mean. I've heard whispers. You're getting some heat.
我正在妥善處理
I'm taking care of it.
所以 你覺得我們在這個問題上 想得狹隘了?
So,you,uh,think we have a tunnel vision problem?
我覺得 我們當然願意相信 自己可以救那些孩子
I think we'd like to believe that we could save those kids,
但 看看他是怎麼對那些母親的
but look what he does to the mothers.
極大的憤怒
A lot of anger.
他很可能也對孩子下了同樣的毒手
He's probably doing the same thing to the children.
他自己的孩子
His own children.
也許
Maybe.
Garcia提供了很有意思的信息
Garcia said something interesting.
金髮藍眼嬰兒在收養中能要高價
Blondhaired,blueeyed babies get top dollar in the adoption system.
所有的母親都是...
All the mothers...
金髮藍眼
Have blond hair and blue eyes.
這你一定會滿意的 這人再好不過了
You're gonna love this. This guy, he has like the best.
誰也比不上
Like there is no better.
他就像是能通上帝
He has like this access to god.
他不想獨佔 想奉獻
He doesn't want to hang on to it. He wants to give it away.
還有多遠? 就快到了
How much further? Not much.
那就是上帝之愛的意義 你知道的 是分享
Because that's what god's love is, you know,it's sharing.
是無私奉獻不求回報
It's giving everything you have of yourself away and not expecting anything in return.
我們到哪了?
Where are we?
就這 寶貝 就是我們要來的地方
Right here,baby, right where we need to be.
她成吧 是吧? 這是你要找到那種妞吧?
She's good,right? That's the kindof y?
她很完美
She's perfect.
我知道希望渺茫 但Monica的父母 說她之前正要去西部
I know it's a long shot, but monica's parents said that she was heading west.
也許她被綁架時 已經按計劃走了部分旅程了
Maybe she made it part of the way when she was kidnapped.
何不把她的DNA和 周圍幾個州的領養記錄比對一下?
So why not run her dna against adoption records in surrounding states?
你在開玩笑嗎? 你老有才了
Are you kidding? I think you're.
嘿 JJ 如果我們找到這個小姑娘 她會怎麼樣?
Hey,jj,if we find this little girl, what's gonna happen to her?
如果在領養的過程中有非法操作
If something illegal transpires the adoption process,
法庭會將其判為無效  孩子會交還給最近的血親
whatthe court nullifies it, the child gets returned to the closest blood relative.
告訴你一句吧 我見過她祖父母了
If it helps, i have met with the grandparents.
他們人都非常好
They're wonderful ople.
哦 我相信他們一定是 我只是...
Oh,i'm sure they are. It's just...
我也不知道 我... 我父母都不在了
I don't know,i... I lost my parents.
當然了 父母走的時候 我比她大
Granted,i was older than she is,but...
但... 讓我撐過去的 是我身邊至親的人
如果Monica的女兒正生活在一個 不錯的家庭 而我們把她帶走
If monica's daughter is with a good family and we take her away from them...
是否弊大於利? 對
Are we doing more harm than good? Yeah.
Garcia 我想我們沒有選擇
Garcia,i don't think we have a choice.
那是他們的孫女啊 他們有自己的權利
These people have a right to their granddaughter.
你是對的  這太難受了
You're right. This sucks.
是啊 請馬上 謝謝
Yes,right away,please. Thank you.
我打電話給兒童保護機構讓他們把 嬰兒死亡的資料送來
I just called cps, asked them to send over infant mortality files.
讓我們可以排除另外一種可能性 很好
那是什麼? 你的側寫
What's that? Your profile.
我不同意你的分析
I disagree with your analysis.
Hotch 你是認真的嗎?
Hotch,are you serious?
這不是回顧法律的文章 只是初步的分析 讓大家產生更多思路
It's not a law review article, t mething hfor us to brainstorm.
但你僅專注在一個方面 Morgan 產前用藥只顯示 有妻子或是女友的存在
But you only focused on one angle,morgan, of a wife or a girlfriend.
我們需要更多的建議
We need more options.
只要作出足夠的排除 我就能立刻向你提出
Which i can give you once we make the proper deductions.
Hotch 你這是讓我猜啊
hotch,you're asking me we need to guess.
Morgan 要使側寫能夠有用
Morgan,in order for the profile to be useful,
就必須要給出多種關於不明疑犯可能 正在做什麼的方案 重寫
it has to generate multiple scenarios about what the unsub is doing. Rewrite it.
我們找到他了 Monica Winmar的女兒
We got her. Monica winmar's daughter.
她四年前被人收養 現在改名叫Lisa
She was adopted 4 years ago. She's lisa now.
Garcia是怎麼找到她的? 不是交叉比對了 整個新墨西哥系統堛爾禤げ?
How did garcia find her? She crossreferenced the entire new mexico system.
她不在新墨西哥 在亞利桑那
She wasn't in new mexico. She was in arizona.
所有的母親都在新墨西哥被綁 被棄屍 但他把嬰兒留在亞利桑那
So all the mothers were abducted and dumped in new mexico, but he keeps the babies in arizona.
他知道警察會在州界停止搜索
He knows the police with stop looking at the state line.
領養中介機構會是我們找到 不明嫌犯的最佳途徑
The adoption agency's gonna be our best lead to the unsub.
領養是誰經手的? 那是第二個大意外
Who handled the case? That's bombshell number 2.
她不是通過中介機構被領養
she didn't go through an agency.
而是被不知什麼人丟在了一間教堂
She was dropped off anonymously at a church.
醫院和教堂是安全的天堂
Hospitals and churches are safe havens.
你可以把孩子丟在那  沒人會問你什麼問題
You can drop a baby off, no questions asked.
兒童保護機構會尋找最直接的親屬
Child protection services would look for the closest relative.
但也只限於本州界內
Another search that ends at the state line.
如果兒童保護機構尋找未果 嬰兒就會像Lisa一樣被送去寄養
And if cps doesn't find one,the baby will go into foster care, which is what happened to lisa.
她是幸運的 一個月內就被領養了
She was lucky. The adoption process happened within a month.
不明嫌犯明明有機會 賣孩子賺錢
So,this unsub had the opportunity to make money off this infant.
但他卻沒有 把孩子丟在教堂 是因為他知道州政府會做妥善安排
He doesn't, drops it off at a church because he knows the state will take good care of it.
想得還真周到
That's awfully considerate.
除去殺人 不明嫌犯的任何行為 都與性虐待狂不符 和我的側寫一致
Outside the murders, nothing about this unsub's behavior profiles like a sexl dist... As i wrote.
嗯 Morgan說得對 這是一個照顧者 一個媽媽的行為
Yeah,morgan's right.
我們的不明嫌犯可能會是女性嗎?
Could our unsub be a woman?
呃 只有男性才會如此折磨受害者
Uh,only a man would torture his victims this much.
男性會沉迷於如此暴力 女性則不然
Men get off on this kind of violence. Women don't.
他也可能結了婚 他的妻子會被迫順從 參與照顧那些媽媽們
He could be married, though,his wife being a passive participant, taking care of the moms.
還有嬰兒們 沒錯 我們得分頭行動
And the babies. All right. Weeed to split up.
我們要分別向新墨西哥和 亞利桑那州警給出側寫
We'll give the profile he a the w mexico state police.
Reid Rossi Prentiss 你們趕去鳳凰城
Morgan你留下來和我一起完成側寫
你覺得怎麼樣?
how are you feeling?
糟透了
Terrible.
你是什麼問題? 什麼? 你什麼意思?
What are you on? What? What are you talking about?
他綁架我們的時候 大家都有點問題
When he takes us, we're all on something.
我是嗜酒成癮 那你是什麼問題?
I was an alcoholic. So,what are you on?
吸毒
Crack.
我叫Carol
I'm carol.
我叫Julie
I'm julie.
來 這有些水 過來喝點
Here. Here's some water. Come drink some.
這是那種嚴愛強制戒癮所嗎?
Is this some kind of tough love detox?
哦 那是怎麼回事?
Oh,what is that?
這就像太陽一樣 為我們補充 維生素D 讓我們保持健康
It's like the sun. It gives us vitamin d. It keeps us healthy.
他們不能強行把我們關在這
Well,they can't make us stay here.
嘿 放我出去!
Hey,let me out!
我要回家! 還我衣服! 還我手機!
I want to go home! I want my clothes! I want my phone!
讓我從這出去! 讓我出去!
Let me out of here! Let me out!
他幹嘛這麼做?
Why is he doing this?
他想要什麼?
What does he want?
你的孩子
Your baby.
我沒懷孕
I'm not pregnant.
你會的
You will be.
我們要找的不明嫌犯是一對夫婦
The unsubs that we are looking for are a couple.
這位男性疑犯 很可能有性暴力的歷史
Now,the man in the relationship most likely has a history of sexual violence.
起初是跟蹤 然後升級為襲擊和強姦
He started with stalking, and then moved his way up to assault and rape.
當他找到他妻子的時候 這些暴力行為暫時停止了
And that violent streak ended temporarily when he found his wife.
他們結婚的第一年  她向他的虐待屈服
For the first years of their marriage,
去找那些反覆進出急診室 有明顯受婚後虐待徵兆的妻子
look for wives who came into the e.R.Repeatedly and with obvious signs of spousal abuse,
你們很可能要追溯到5年前
but you are gonna have to go back about 5 years.
這是因為 第一起綁架發生的時候 她就停止進出急診了
That's because around the time of the first abduction, the visits stopped.
性虐狂不能從自願參與的 對像身上獲得滿足
The sexual sadist can't find satisfaction from a willing participant.
不斷對她施暴 但終有一天 不殺死她就再無法升級
He eventually got to a place where he couldn't escalate his violence against her without killing her,
所以她和他達成了協議
so she made him a deal.
他可以綁架 強姦 殺死這些 離家出走的女孩 她則留下孩子
He gets to kidnap, rape,and kill each of the runaways, and she gets to keep the children.
她一直在給受害者提供 一系列的產前處方藥
She's been giving the victims a series of prescription prenatal drugs.
你們調查的重點應該在相關領域 護士 助產士...
那做妻子的需要這些孩子
The wife needs these children.
起初 孩子是她的生命線  保障她能活下來
At first,they were the lifeline that kept her alive.
只要他還有其他的虐待對像 她就能躲過他強烈的慾望
As long as he had other targets for his abuse, she avoided his rage.
但 如果這些孩子能保護她免受虐待 為什麼她要把他們送去被領養呢?
So if these children protect her from abuse, why is she putting them up for adoption?
我們相信不明嫌犯只想要 和他們長得像的孩子
We believe the unsubs want children who resemble them physically,
沒有人會質疑是否他們親生的孩子
who no one would question as their own.
所有離家出走的女孩都是金髮 也就是說不明嫌犯很可能也是
All of the runaways have been blond, which means the unsub
但我們在領養系統塈鋮鴘 第一個孩子是棕髮
不管外表上的特徵是什麼 例如  眼睛或皮膚的顏色
e sil the color of the eyes, the skin type
如果孩子不具備這些  他或她最後會進入寄養體系
if the baby doesn't have it, he or she ends up in the foster care system,
性虐狂的妻子需要發洩途徑 作為一種逃避機制
wives of sexual sadists need outlets as a denial mechanism
來應付她們的伴侶的所作所為
to cope with what their partners are doing.
成為一個母親 特別是照顧無依無靠的 嬰兒 就是這個女人的應對方式
And motherhood, especially taking care of a helplesinfant is this woman's way of coping.
你找到她了? 我們找到了
We have.
她怎麼樣? 她很好
How is she? She's great.
她被一對年輕的夫婦領養了
She was adopted by a young couple.
沒有生理或心理創傷的報告
那我們什麼時候可以要回她?
So when can we take her?
現在我們只和她父母的律師聯繫過 但法律是站在你們這邊的
Right now we're in touch with her adoptive parents' lawyer, but the law is on your side.
我們能和父母談談嗎? 我們可以和他們商量
Can we talk to the parents? We could discuss this but the with them.
他們不希望進一步的接觸
They don't want to initiate contact.
他們經歷的已經很多了
They've been through a lot right now.
他們是她的父母 當然不想放棄她
They're her parents. Of course they don't want to give her up.
那如果她想見他們 我們考慮滿足 但我們是她的家人
Well,if she wants to see them,then we can work that out, but we are her family.
絕對的
Absolutely.
不 等等 這是不是有些風險在堶?
no,wait. What are the risks here?
如果我們要回她 會不會傷害她?
E we hurting her?
這不好說 有些孩子適應得很好
It's impossible to tell. Some kids do great.
有些孩子會有問題
Others have trouble.
但 我們為什麼要談風險? 她是Monica的女兒啊
But why are we talking about risks? She's monica's daughter.
Conrad... 她又不是他們的骨血
Conrad... She's not their blood.
別說了
Stop it.
謝謝你 Jareau警探
Thank you,agent jareau.
我丈夫和我需要商量一下這事
But my husband and i, we need to discuss this.
這是什麼? 這是我們在找的規律
What's this? It's the pattern i've been looking for.
不明疑犯隱藏處理媽媽們的蹤跡
The unsubs hid their tracks with the mothers,
但他們棄嬰卻不是那麼小心
but they weren't so careful with the abandoned babies.
你找到更多的孩子了嗎? 基因的角度沒 但綁架的角度有
我集中了所有那些
I gathered all the records for all infants
3位母親被害2周內進入 寄養系統的嬰兒記錄
who entered into foster care in a 2week window following each mother's death.
然後 我將範圍縮小至其中 被拋棄在教堂的嬰兒
Then i narrowed it down to babies that were abandoned at churches.
到這就要開始猜了
This is where the guesswork begins.
Monica Winmar的女兒是被 丟在一個長老派教會的教堂的
Monica's winmar's daughter was abandoned at a presbyterian church.
我們假設不明嫌犯 或至少他的妻子 是個長老派教會信徒
Let's assume the unsub, or the wife at least, is presbyterian.
這就意味著所有他們不想要的孩子 都會被丟在同樣教派教堂 對吧?
That means all other unwanted children are gonna be left at the same denomination,right?
這樣一來範圍縮小到 被三個長老教會收留的三個孩子
That narrows it down to 3 babies left at 3 different presbyterian churches
都在方圓二十里內
all within this 20mile radius.
就是他們住的地方
This is where they live.
你推斷的這些孩子 你看過資料嗎?
These kids you deduced tohave you looked at their files?
不 我現在還在追蹤教堂 怎麼了?
No. Right now i've only been tracking churches. Why?
因為你剛剛發現了另一種模式
Because you just uncovered another pattern.
嗯 我們準備出發了 2小時內到鳳凰城
Yeah, we're packing up now. We can be in phoenix in about 2 hours.
你確定嗎?
You sure about this?
Reid發現的小孩的名字說明了一切
The names of the babies reid found tells us everything.
Lisa Elizabeth Amanda
Lisa,elizabeth,amanda.
我們側寫有一類他們自己養 有一類他們給人收養
We profiled there'd be a type they'd keep and a type they'd put into foster care.
他們要留男孩子
They're keeping the boys.
是時候了
It's time.
你幹什麼?
What are you doing?
你幹什麼? 嘿 你去哪? 回來
What are you doing? Hey,where are you going? Come back!
你回來 求你了
You have to come back! Please!
這種時候 他們從不待在這兒
They never stay for this part.
不不不 你不是真的要...
No,no,no,no. You're not actually
是的
yes...I am.
他們給我催產了
They've induced.
我要怎麼辦?
What am i supposed to do?
來幫我
You help me.
一千...
11,000...
兩千... 不不不 對不起 我不行
21,000... No,no,no,i'm sorry, i can't.
我幫不了你 我... 三千...
I can't help you.I can't. 31,000...
我病了 我很不好
I'm sick. I'm not well.
我需要... 我做不到 Julie 聽我說
I need a... I can't do it. Julie,listen to me.
你在聽嗎? 是 我在聽
Are you listening to me? Yes. Yes.
如果這孩子生不下來的話
If this baby doesn't make it...
他們就會殺了我
They are going to kill me.
他們殺了我 下一個就輪到你 你懂了嗎?
And once they've killed me, they are going to move on to you. Do you understand?
好吧 好吧 我們要怎麼做
Ok. Ok. What do we do?
JJ 幫我找這些生育專家來問話
Jj,i need you to call these fertility specialists and get them over here for interviews.
是 我知道 Hotch想著重查 不明嫌犯給受害人吃的產前藥
Yeah,i know. Hotch wants to focus on the prenatal drugs the unsubs are giving the victims.
覺得能據此建立起新的嫌犯群 他昨天就想弄完了
He thinks we can build a new suspect pool, and he wants it done yesterday.
這埵釣潃雄的名字 該先縮小下範圍嗎?
There's 2 pages of names here. Shouldn't we narrow it down?
JJ 就照做行嗎?
Jj,just do it,ok?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你還好嗎?
Is everything ok?
來這兒後 Hotch對我特別嚴 我不知道為什麼
Hos be on ever since we got here, and for the life of me, i can't figure out why.
好吧 我也許知道
Oh,i might know.
這案子之前 Strauss主管到BAU來了
The ghbeck this case, chief strauss stopped by the b.A.U.
他們關著房門 氣氛好像有點緊張
They were behind closed doors, and it seemed like it got a little tense.
好吧 上面的頭兒盯著他 他肯定知道要發生什麼
Well,the bureau's been on him for a while.
是啊 現在他們盯著他的每個決定
對Hotch來說 那真是...煎熬
For hotch,that's... Hell.
Dekeyser醫生 我們認為 她不是因病才服下產前藥
Dr. Dekeyser, we don't think she's getting these prenatal drugs as a patient.
你認為她自己給自己開的處方
You're thinking she's writing the scrip for these herself.
差不多
Something like that.
她可能不太知道她在做什麼
Then she wouldn't be very knowledgeable about what she's doing.
某些藥有嚴重的副作用
Some of these drugs have serious side effects.
比起這些 我可以開很多療效更好的藥
There's dozens of meds i would prescribe before these, all of them more effective.
所以她為什麼用這個?
So why would she use these?
我猜 是她能拿得到的吧
My guessthese are the ones she had access to.
催孕藥是混合物 你懷孕之前得一直混合它們
Fertility drugs are a cocktail, and you keep remixing the cocktail until you get pregnant.
網上到處都是這類信息 被她給找到了
The information is out there on the internet. She found the right one.
所以她也許是因為別的病開這些藥的
So the woman was prescribed these drugs maybe for some other illness
結果發現它們能催孕?
and figured out that they helped carry a baby to term.
正是這樣
最後個問題 這些藥還治什麼病?
Tlat o er ddo these drugs treat?
好 我可以 我可以的
Ok. I can do this. I can do this.
怎麼了?
沒什麼 你讓我想起我自己
You remind me of me.
我可以的 Carol? 求你了 要醒著
I can do this. Carol? Please?
好吧 就 就注意聽我的聲音 好嗎?
Ok,justjust focus on the sound of my voice,ok?
你行嗎? 我在這兒
Can you do that? I'm here.
Carol 跟我講講之前那個女人
Caell meouwoma who was here before me.
她怎麼了?
What happened to her?
她總是... 流產
She miscarried... A lot.
最後生了個女孩兒 他們不喜歡女孩兒
They don't le girls.
這也不是你第一次 對吧? 嗯
This isn yourfirst time,is it? No.
發生了什麼?
What happened?
他沒活下來
He didn't make it.
我很抱歉
即使孩子沒了 他們也會讓你活著
They let you live even if you lose him.
他們要男孩兒
They want those boys.
好吧 好吧
Ok. Ok,hey.
聽著 我不知道該怎麼做 求你 求你告訴我怎麼辦
Listen,i don't know what to do,ok, so please,please, just tell me what to do.
我張得有多大了? 什麼意思?
How dilated am i? 'Tnow what that means.
把你的手指並起來
Just put your fingers in a row and...
量一下 等等
Measure me. Wait...
哦 天哪
Oh,my god.
好吧 哦 我的天
Ok... Oh,my god.
四個 四根手指 我...
It's 4. it's 4 fingers.And i
哦 天哪 那是頭嗎?
oh,god, is that the head?
哦 上帝 這是怎麼回事?
Oh,my god, what does that mean?
這是... 要生了
It means... It's time to push.
這是什麼?
What is this?
這是戰術逮捕計劃 我要你給這案子寫一個
It's a tactical arrest plan. I'd like you to write it up for this case.
你要我寫 在保護孩子的前提下 如何抓捕不明嫌犯?
You want me to write up how we apprehend these unsubs without risking the lives of the children.
是
Yes.
Hotch 我帶過無數次抓捕行動
Hotch,i've led dozens of tactical assaults.
你之前從沒讓我寫過
You've never made me write up one of these before.
那是因為每次我都幫你寫了
That's because i always do it for you after each case.
你知道嗎?
You know what?
Strauss給你施壓 我也為你不平
I'm sorry strauss is coming down on you.
這和Strauss無關 真的? 我看不是
This is not about strauss. Really? I disagree.
我知道你現在擔子特別重
Look,i understand that you're under the gun.
但我不得不說 我並不是很吃驚
But i gotta say it. I'm really not all that surprised.
在華盛頓 一群警察擊倒了不明嫌犯 你卻走開了
I've watched you walk away from a bunch of cops gunning down unsubs in d.C.
在路易斯維爾 你手無寸鐵 就走進人質挾持現場
You walked in unprotected to a hostage situation in louisville.
局媟穔M會擔心你
Of course the bureau's worried about you.
夥計 我都很擔心你
Man,i'm worried about you.
但是 雖然你身在放大鏡下
But just because you're the one who's under the magnifying glass,
卻不意味著 我不能做好自己的工作
that doesn't mean i can't do my job.
Morgan 你有很大一部分工作 是我幫你完成的
Morgan,there's a big part of your job that i do for you
因為我不希望你為文書和政治工作分心
because i don't need you worried about paperwork and politics.
我要你專心抓不明嫌犯
I need you in the field d focused and catching the next unsub.
但我不能再那麼做了
But i can't do that anymore.
我無需證明自己對你的命令 你必須聽我的
I don't have to justify my orders to you, and you do have to follow them.
如果你的命令言之有理 我向來聽從
I've always followed your orders when they made sense.
好吧 如果你覺得這個有問題 現在說
Well,if you have a problem with this one,tell me now.
你說了算
Yos.
Garcia需要盡快跟我們通話
Garcia needs to talk to us asap.
生育專家告訴Rossi探員
那些產前藥還能治一種病
And his short list of one disease these prenatal drugs also treat.
就是乳腺癌 黃體酮 它莫西芬能減緩蔓延 胃復安和多潘立酮
Breast cancer. Progesterone,tamoxifen slow the spread, metoclopramide and domperidone
如果我沒記錯 是止嘔的
are for antinausea if i remember correctly.
如果這女人有乳腺癌 還能懷孕嗎?
If this woman has breast cancer,would she be able to get pregnant?
可以 但必須做出犧牲 怎麼犧牲?
How dedicated?
她得進行化療 那相當痛苦
Well,she'd have to go off chemotherapy. She'd be in a lot of pain.
但她肯定會嘗試 她的全部就是孩子 那是她的目標
But she'll try anyway. Her whole life is children. That's heroal.
第一個逃犯 Monica 是什麼時候被拐的? 五年前
The first runaway, when washe abducted? 5 years ago.
五六年前亞利桑那有多少乳腺癌病人懷孕?
How many breast cancer patients in arizona got pregnant 5 to 6 years ago?
我看看 不多 七個
Uh,let me see. Not a lot. 7.
其中有幾個嫁給了有性暴力史的傢伙?
how many of those patients are married to a man with a history of sexual violence?
只有一個 Robert和Linda Reimann
Just onerobert and linda reimann.
哦上帝 怎麼了?
Oh,jeez. What?
她八個月的時候流產了 不得不分娩
She lost the baby in month 8. she had to go through labor anyway.
這種精神和心理的雙重創傷 我們有了應激源
Well,that kind of physical and emotional trauma, there's our stressor.
Garcia 是男孩兒嗎? 嗯 他們還給他起名叫Michael
Garcia, was the baby a boy? Yeah. They even named himmichael.
死亡證明上肯定有名字
There has to be a name on the death certificate.
醫生鼓勵母親和死嬰的接觸 我...
Doctors encourage bonding between mothers and stillborns. I...
志願參加了一個新媽媽咨詢小組
Volunteer with a new mom counseling group.
據說這樣能幫她們應對失落感
They say it helps them cope with feelings of loss.
這位不明顯然不能應對 因此只好再造
Well,this unsub can't cope, so she's recreating them.
哦 加油 就快好了 再用點力
Ok,come on, you're almost there. Just pus push!
哦 天哪
Oh,my god.
男孩女孩? 是個男孩
Is it a boy or a girl? It's a boy.
你來了 你做到了
You're here. You made it.
不
No.
不要 不 不 求你啦 別碰他 求你了
Don't. No! No,please, leave her alone. Please!
求你 求你 就一分鐘 求你了
Please,please,please, just wait one minute. Please,please!
是個男孩
It's a boy.
Michael
Michael.
長官 這是不明嫌犯的地址
Ok,commander,this here Is the unsub's address.
五年前 她失去孩子的時候
Now,5 years ago when the wife lost their child,
丈夫開始用信用卡付款家庭裝修
The husband started paying For home renovations with his credit card.
淋浴 廁所 瓷磚 護欄 但是並沒有在他的後院
Shower,toilet,tile, and mesh fencing Which he did not put up in his backyard.
他在建他的地牢
He was building his dungeon.
沒有允許他們擴建的許可
No permits were filed for additional building on the property,
所以入口肯定在房子
So the entrance must be inside the house.
要守幾個出入口?
How many doors are there to cover?
有2個 一個在前一個在後
There's 2one in the front, one in the back.
我們有逮捕令嗎?
We have the arrest warrants?
20分鐘前傳真出去了
Faxed over 20 minutes ago.
Morgan 你怎麼計劃的?
Morgan,what's your plan?
我覺得不該強行進入
I think we should do a soft entry.
在父母不知道的情況下 看看能不能救回那些孩子
See if we can get the kids out Before the parents even know what's happening.
你先進去?
You'd be in the door first?
你還有其它主意嗎?
Do you have another idea?
讓Prentiss和JJ先進去
Send prentiss and jj in first.
孩子更容易相信女人
Children are more likely to trust a woman, and we need that presence.
我們不知道房子埵釵h少小孩
We don't know how many kids are in the house.
他們可能會用他們做人質
I mean,the parents could take a hostage.
但如果我們硬闖進去 這個情況就肯定會發生
But if we go in hot, That would definitely happen.
Hotch是對的 只有這樣了
Hotch is right. This is the way.
沒事 沒事 我們是警察 我們是好人
It's ok. It's ok. we're the police. We're the good guys.
你可以和我出來嗎? 好的 好的
Can you come outside with me? Ok. ok.
Hotch 我們找到一個男孩
Hotch,we've got one boy accounted for.
他正在出來 但地下室堨i能有更多人
He's on his way out to you, But there could still be more in the basement.
FBI 你的妻子呢?
Fbi. Where's your wife?
在嬰兒房 Rossi
In the nursery. Rossi.
Hotch 走
Hotch. Go.
我就知道這會結束
I knew this would end.
我知道你們會過來 奪走我的一切
I always knew you'd come to our door And take this away.
女士 請你把孩子給我好嗎
Ma'am,why don't you give me the baby.
我們可以談一談
We can talk about it.
為什麼我要同意這樣做呢?
Why would i want to do that?
你這麼做是不對的 你肯定知道
What you've been doing is wrong. You must know that.
老天 拜託了 讓我們出去
Oh,god,please,please get us out of here!
哦 感謝上帝 感謝上帝
Oh! oh,thank god. thank god.
沒有危險了
We're all clear here.
沒事了 沒事了 你們安全了 跟我來
It's ok. it's ok,you're safe. come with me.
不行 我不能丟下她
But no,i can't leave her.
安全了 但我們需要醫生
All secure, but we need medical.
這是我唯一剩下的了
This is all i have left.
你明白嗎?
Do you understand?
我丈夫恨我
My husband hates me.
沒有人可以幫我照顧他
There's nobody here that can help me with him,
你看現在這種情況
With this, with any of it.
我只剩下他了
He's all i have.
Linda
Linda.
拜託 你要為小孩考慮一下
Please. I need you to think about the baby right now.
你得了第四期乳腺癌
You're suffering from stage 4 breast cancer.
你把你的藥給了關在下面的女人
You've given your medication to the women That have been locked up downstairs.
你沒有多少時間了
You don't have a lot of time left.
我知道你希望有人可以永遠記得你 對嗎?
I know you want somebody who will always remember you,don't you?
孩子的名字是Michael 是嗎?
The baby's name is michael,right?
是的
Yeah.
Michael會記得你的
Michael will remember you.
他會知道 是你幫他來到這個世界上
He's gonna know that you helped bring him into the world.
他會記得了 他會一直問起你的
That's a part of him now. And he will always ask about you,
即使很久很久以後
Long after you're gone.
你真的相信嗎?
Do you really believe that?
是的
I do.
我會是個好媽媽
I would have been a wonderful mother.
那就證明看看
Then prove it.
讓他走吧
Let him go.
我兒子在哪? 我們正在找他
Where's my son? We're looking for him.
拜託 請你們保護他
Please,don't let anything happen to him.
看 他在這 他很好
Look,he's here. He's fine.
他沒事
He's ok.
你看你 多漂亮呀
You are beautiful, aren't you?
我和Lisa的養父母談過了
I spoke with lisa's adoptive parents.
他們願意和你談談 但他們不願意放棄監護權
They've agreed to talk to you. They're not willing to give up custody,
但他們希望Lisa能認識一下爺爺奶奶
But they do want lisa to know her grandparents.
我們可以接受
Yeah,wewe can live with that.
我叫你們過來是因為...
The reason why i wanted you to come by Was...
在生下Lisa的一年前 Monica生了個兒子
a year before giving birth to lisa, Monica had a son.
已經和你的女兒比對過DNA了
We've already matched his dna to your daughter.
和他最近的親戚應該擁有監護權
The closest relative should take custody.
想見見他嗎?
Would you like to meet him?
他叫什麼名字? Michael
What's his name? Michael.
Michael
Michael.
坐
Have a seat.
局媊控o我領導團隊的能力出了問題
The bureau thinks that my ability To lead this team has been compromised.
你覺得呢?
What do you think?
有時候我會質疑你 Hotch
Sometimes i question you, hotch.
但到頭來 我卻不由欽佩你
But at the end of the day, i do respect you.
你是團隊的領導 我的工作就是支持你
You're the leader of this team, And my job is to have your back.
局堿搨囿漱ㄛO這個
Well,that's not important to the bureau.
自從被Foyet襲擊後 他們一直在質疑我
They've been questioning me since foyet's attack.
他們也並不是都錯了 我已經盡力了
And they're not entirely wrong. I've tried to do my best,
現在重要的是 如果Strauss找人取代我
But what matters now is if strauss replaces me,
整個行為分析部會受到審查
This whole unit will come under scrutiny.
隊員會被重新分配崗位 經費也會被削減
Members will be reassigned, budgets will be cut.
Hotch 沒人能取代你
Come on,hotch, nobody's gonna replace you.
和Strauss爭一爭啊 我會站在你這邊
Fight strauss. i'll go to the mat for you.
其他人也是一樣的  Morgan 這行不通的
So will everybody else. you know that. Morgan,it won't work.
做出這樣的決定 有他們的理由
Decisions like this have their own momentum...
除非我退出
Unless i step down.
退出 你在說什麼?
Step down? what are you talking about?
我這個週末會辭去部門主管的職位
I'm resigning as unit chief at the end of the week.
什麼? 不行!
What? No!
Hotch 沒錯 好吧
Hotch,look,yeah,ok,
有時候我是不同意你的行動
Sometimes your actions, i may disagree with them,
但不能因為這樣 你就要離開這個團隊
But it's not enough for you to leave this team.
我不是離開這個團隊 只是不再是領導者
I'm not leaving the team, I'm just no longer in charge.
你是
You are.
我?
Me?
我有機會在紐約成為部門主管 但我拒絕了
look,i had the chance to be unit chief in new york, And i said no.
因為我喜歡這個團隊
I turned it down because i like this team.
Strauss不能就這樣炒了你
Strauss can't just fire you like this.
她可以把我調職
She can reassign me.
如果我從內部提拔 就可以不必被調任
And we can avoid that if i promote internally.
這是不對的
This is wrong.
這是唯一保證我們團隊不解散的方法
It's the only way to keep the team together.
所以這些...
so all of this
所以你才對我這麼苛刻?
This is why you've been pushing me so hard,huh?
也沒那麼苛刻吧
I haven't been pushing you that hard.
Morgan 我需要你現在就告訴我 你願意嗎?
Morgan,i need to know Right nowWill you do this?
這只是暫時的
This would be temporary.
只要我們抓住Foyet 就可以一切恢復正常
Once we catch foyet, All this goes back to normal.
那開始行動吧
Let's get started.
這些是什麼?
What's all this?
都是工作 除非你有其他計劃
This is the job, Unless you have other plans.
今晚沒有
Not tonight.
犯罪心理 第五季 第05集 從生到死
== 結束 ==
Criminal Minds Season05 Episode05 Cradle to Grave